{
    "id": "66c3bd5b00254027aeb6d9aad2b7bd92",
    "title": "Both, Either And Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like ………………….. of these two dresses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1666dc09723b454abdd5efee2133ee66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like ………………….. of these. Have you got another one?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "882a4377a3694ec0919faa53dc4b6e89"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. of them have been invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e572a20d0bc4531bc009913194f5980"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited …………………. of them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "neither",
                "either"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7473c419f953432a874d50a9499eccfc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t invited ………………….. of them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a1eb34ad5eb49c6aca379fedeeda908"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ………………… eager to hear the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3d29c125e834916b5d792ec75b7fdd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Martin and James are brilliant boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2420b7ba1214b6a831ae9789681f689"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you ……………….’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "667ee80477b746d6800424642c135da1"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Martin nor James turned up today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a3830c1e5a5a4647908500931d33e848"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. intelligent nor hardworking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30ad83eb962f41bf86c4c1dd60ff0ffc"
        }
    ]
}